

# EMANOIL ORIANA

#### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

ADDRESS: Bucharest, Romania

PHONE: +40732 713 030

EMAIL: oriana.emanoil@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO: www.oriana.ro

()

github.com/Jinxulete

8

live:.cid.9bf1d679840d09de

in

in/oriana-elena-emanoilcosma-338487111

#### **EDUCATION**

#### The Faculty of Philosophy

University of Bucharest 2014-2018

#### **Fashion Design**

"Nicolae Tonitza" Fine Arts High School Bucharest 2011-2014

#### INTRODUCTION

I am a Front-end developer in love with programming and passionate about creating an amazing user-experience. I have a strong knowledge of the inner workings of the web and the ability to bring websites to life from a mock-up to a fully functional web app.

#### EXPERIENCE

# Front-end Developer & QA Tester at Class It Oursourcing

03/2018-10/2023

Developing and designing webpages maintaining height performance and adaptive modules.

Write clean, well structured maintainable code that conforms with accepted standards and make sure that it is practical and aesthetic at the same time. Manual & automatic Testing Websites and IOS Applications, using Postman & Selenium. Writing testing scenarios and documentations and fix the bugs.

Technologies used:

PHP, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Visual Studio, CSS3, GIT, HTML5, Bootstrap, Angularjs, ReactJS, Postman, Selenium;

### QA Testing at PayScout

06/2014-12/2017

Testing credit cards, make transactions, use Selenium to make manual testing into automatic, compare the results and fix the errors.

Technologies used: JavaScript, Selenium, Postman;

#### Game Tester at Ea Games

Testing video games on ps3, ps4, XP0, pc, phone.

02/2012-04/2014

## COOL THINGS I MADE

<u>sigurantapenet</u> Presentation website build with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and

React.

#### SKILLS

HTML/CSS JavaScript

React

Postman

Selenium









